vebtoday.com 2010-06-12

# vebtoday - Privacy

This privacy statement has been produced to express **Vebtoday.com** ’s assurance of privacy. The practices concerning collecting of information to be displayed on **Vebtoday.com** are explained below.

Information Automatically Logged   
Your IP address may be used to collect wide-ranging demographic information or for the purpose of detecting any problems that may arise, pertaining to our server or website administration. 

Your IP address or demographic information is never shared with anyone or disclosed to anyone or any third-party.

Cookies   
Various methods are employed to gather this data. "Cookies" are used to distinguish and relate non personal data to individuals. These are "small strings of text" that are stored in browsers; cookies are not programs that can damage your computer. If you wish to stop the cookie functionality on your browser, you may do so. 

Our Site uses cookies to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly. We also use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, and to save your login information so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site. Information collected using cookies is never shared with anyone or disclosed to third parties. 

Advertisers   
We work with various third party advertising networks. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by advertising network, and we do not have access to this information. 

To find out more about how the ad network manages the privacy of information in conjunction with serving ads on this site, 

Please go to:   
Google  
Advertising.com   
Mediaturf.com  
Revenue.net   
Mamma Media Solutions 

Registration Forms   
Vebtoday.com does not collect personally identifiable information about individuals, except when individuals provide such information on a voluntary basis in our registration forms. 

Contact information from the registration forms is used to get in touch with the customer when necessary. Contact information is never shared with anyone or disclosed to third parties. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. 

This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. This data is also used to serve banner ads. 

External Links   
This site contains links to other sites. Vebtoday.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

Public Forums   
This site makes chat rooms, opinion polls, and/or news available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

Security   
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. We make every effort to maintain quality of service and prevent misuse. 

Children's Guidelines (Children under 13)   
This site collects and uses personally identifiable information without prior verifiable parental consent. This site allows children to post or distribute any personally identifiable information without first obtaining verifiable parental consent. 

Contacting the Web Site   
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us. 

For any other questions, please contact us on this email address: [webmaster@vebtoday.com](mailto:webmaster@vebtoday.com)
